xxxblackbook.com 2014-06-26

# XXX BlackBook - Adult Dating Website - Find Sexy Singles, Men, Women, Couples For Local Sex, Dating, Online Dating

### XXXBlackBook.com Privacy Policy:

We are committed to protecting our users' privacy!

We at XXXBlackBook.com offer this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to inform Users of the XXXBlackBook.com ("Website") how we define, collect, use and disclose the personal information you provide to us. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to alter this Policy at any time. Alterations shall become effective immediately once posted on the Website. We will notify you of a substantive change to this Policy by posting a notice of such substantial change on the home page of the Website and we may also email you to notify you of such changes. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute your acceptance of the revised privacy policy.

By providing personal information to us, and by using the Website or Service, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.

Please read this Policy carefully and save it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, you should leave the Website and discontinue use of the Service immediately. In addition, if you are an individual who wishes to become a Registered User or Member, you must read this Policy and indicate your acceptance of its terms by following the instructions on the [REGISTRATION [http://www.xxxblackbook.com/register]](https://web.archive.org/register) page and check the box labelled "I have read and agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. I confirm I have reached the age of majority in my jurisdiction." 

For the purposes of this Policy, "personal information" shall mean any information that can identify an individual directly or through other reasonable means.

#### 1) Information We Gather Automatically. 

Each time a visitor visits the Website, our servers collect certain non-personal technical information, including, but not necessarily limited to, the visitor's IP Address, referral data and browser/platform type. This information is recorded by the standard operation of XXXBlackBook.com's Internet servers. We also count, track and aggregate a visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at the Website (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Website, etc.). The information collected here cannot identify who you are as an individual. However, we may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, the Website, users or others.

We may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then at our discretion be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers. We will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. 

What are IP Addresses? An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you're surfing the Internet. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, which means that your session will be logged anonymously. 

What are Cookies? We use cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, and to customize advertising and web page content for individual users. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier which we transfer to your hard drive through your web browser when you visit our Website. It enables our own system to recognise you when you visit our Website again and improve our service to you. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of our Website that are visited most frequently. 

This traffic information can be used to enhance the content of our Website and make your use of it easier. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Website. Note that you must enable cookies from XXXBlackBook.com in order to use most functions on the Website. Nevertheless, if you wish to reject our cookies, you can configure your browser to do so (instructions for disabling cookies can be found in our FAQs here. Please note that XXXBlackBook.com allows third parties who are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer in a process that XXXBlackBook.com does not control. Advertisers' uses of cookies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy. Therefore, we suggest that you examine the privacy policies of such advertisers to learn how they may collect, use, share and disclose your personal information. 

#### 2) Information Required for Registration. 

XXXBlackBook.com will identify to you the purposes for which it will collect or use personal information before or at the time the information is collected. The type of personal information we may request depends on and is related to the reason (or purpose) such personal information was provided to us. During the process to become a User of the Website, we ask for general identifying information to provide you with customized service. We gather personal contact information such as screen name, email address, and some demographic information such as age, gender and general geographic location. Any other information you choose to enter, such as your personal interests and preferences and general indications of the type of partner you are looking for using the Service, is completely optional. 

We encourage Users to fill out their profiles as completely as possible, with the understanding that, once entered, contact information is treated anonymously and is not available to other XXXBlackBook.com Users. Any communications from other Users are done via our internal systems, which are used to match the message to you and generate an e-mail notification without disclosing any information aside from your chosen screen name.

The choice to provide us with your personal information is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular information may result in limiting our ability to respond to your inquiries or provide you with the Services you requested. If a new purpose is identified for the use of the information collected, the new purpose will be explained prior to its new use. Unless the new purpose is required by law, your consent is required before information can be used for that purpose. Demographic information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals at any time.

Note that, during the Membership process, third party billing agents will collect personally identifiable information required to process payments for the service. XXXBlackBook.com retains information (name and address) to correctly identify you in dealings with third party billing agents. Additional information gathered by third party billing agents is not controlled by XXXBlackBook.com or this Policy. 

#### 3) Voluntary Inclusion of Personal Information. 

Personally identifiable information that you enter into your profile, that you include in communications with other Members or Users, or that you disclose in any media (text, chat streams, graphical, audio, visual or audio-visual), or that you post or display on the Website is accessible by visitors to the website, and by other Users (Registered Users and Members) of the Website. XXXBlackBook.com is not responsible for any privacy issues arising from your own voluntary posting or transmission of personal information via the Service. You acknowledge and agree that you (not XXXBlackBook.com or our affiliates, advertisers, employees and content providers) shall be solely responsible and liable for all damages, liability or other consequences, foreseen or unforeseen, of all information which you submit, publish, display, disseminate or otherwise communicate through the Website even if a claim for damages or liability should arise after termination of service.

#### 4) Communication. 

The Website directly communicates with Members and Users through email, instant messaging, and in some cases, downloaded executables. This enables Members to receive information when they are not on the Website, so they remain current on internal communication and updates from other Users or from us directly. The Website may also use personally identifiable information within your profile to send information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as special banners and promotions. Should you not wish XXXBlackBook.com to send you information on other services or products, please just contact us using the information provided in section 17 below. 

Members of the Website can directly communicate with you through messaging services that are part of the Service (mail, chat or via comments). We may use personally identifiable information within your profile to send notifications of these communications to you, but your personally identifiable information is not disclosed to other Members by us. 

#### 5) Referrals. 

If you choose to use our external referral service to tell a friend about the Website, we will ask you for your friend's contact information. The Website will automatically send your friend an e-mail inviting them to visit the Website. The Website maintains this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of the referral.

#### 6) Your Use of Other Users' Information. 

You may not use other Users' information for commercial purposes, to send SPAM or SPIM, to harass, to make unlawful threats, or for any other illegal purpose. XXXBlackBook.com reserves the right to terminate the Service to those who misuse other Users' information.

If you receive communications that you find to have violated this Policy, please contact us using the information provided in section 17 below, being sure to include the message text and the User who sent the communication to you.

#### 7) Accuracy of Personal Information, Information Review and Removal. 

We shall make every reasonable effort to ensure your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You are responsible for advising XXXBlackBook.com of any inaccuracies or changes to your personal information. 

Users may modify or remove any of their information associated with their profile at any time by logging into their account and accessing the Edit Profile feature.

Users may, at any time, delete their profiles or remove any images or audio-visual material that they have posted to the Website.

#### 8) Promotion. 

From time to time, XXXBlackBook.com may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events of interest to our users. XXXBlackBook.com may co-sponsor these events with third party organizations, and may be required to share demographic information to be used for the event. Any shared demographic information will not be associated with individual users; it will only be presented as aggregated information. 

In some cases, promotions or sweepstakes that may be of interest to our users may require us to share email information with third party sponsors or partners. A User's personal email information will not be released to any third party organization without the User's express consent and disclosure of the sponsor organization's name, and XXXBlackBook.com will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrant's information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations, and we will ensure that such sponsors agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy. 

Should you not wish to receive notices or be considered for sweepstakes, contests or other events, please contact us using the information provided in section 17 below. 

#### 9) Disclosure and Retention of Personal Information. 

We will only use or disclose your personal information in accordance with the purposes for which it was originally collected unless you have otherwise consented, or when required or permitted by law. We will keep your personal information only for so long as is required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected or as required by law. Except as explained in this Policy, or as otherwise consented to by you, we do not disclose any personal information to third parties. The following are the limited instances where we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  1. When this information must be shared to provide a product or service you have requested.
  2. We need to send the information to companies who work on our behalf to provide a product or service to you.
  3. To investigate and/or enforce violations of our Terms and Conditions and/or this Policy, or to protect our interests in our operation and our legal rights and protections.
  4. To investigate potentially fraudulent or questionable activities.
  5. When required or permitted by law. XXXBlackBook.com (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) independently reserves the right to fully cooperate with requests from any recognized law enforcement authority, and to court orders, requesting or directing XXXBlackBook.com (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) to disclose the identity or other information regarding any person who is using or has used the Website or the Service or has obtained any Content available through or in association with the Website. By accepting this Policy and using the Website and/or the Service, you waive and hold harmless XXXBlackBook.com, our affiliates, content providers, and the operators of the Website from any and all claims resulting from any and all actions taken by any of the foregoing during, or as a result of any law enforcement authority's investigations or inquiries.
  6. In the course of a sale or potential sale, reorganization, consolidation, merger or amalgamation of our business. In order to ensure a smooth transition of the Service in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets or the sale of an individual website owned by XXXBlackBook.com, XXXBlackBook.com may transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale. In the event the transaction proceeds, we will require that the receiving party agree that they will be similarly bound by the provisions of this privacy policy and that they will only use and disclose your personal information as we are similarly entitled under this privacy policy. In the event the sale does not proceed, we will require the potential purchaser to not use or disclose your personal information in any manner whatsoever and to completely erase the same.
  7. Where such disclosure is described elsewhere in this Policy.This Policy does not protect information you post to any online profile, bulletin board, e-note, video chat room, or any other forum accessible to other Users or other sites within XXXBlackBook.com.

#### 10) Location of Personal Information

We are an international organization with servers located in various jurisdictions. As a result, User and Member personal information may be transferred to and stored in Canada, Ireland or elsewhere. We do the best we can to ensure your personal information is protected to the greatest extent possible. However, please note that the jurisdiction in which we store your personal information may not have similar standards for protecting your personal information as are provided for in your country. As well, government organizations from the jurisdiction in which the personal information is stored may have access to your personal information in accordance with the laws of such jurisdiction. 

#### 11) Employee Access to Your Personal Information. 

In the course of daily operations, access to private, sensitive and confidential information is restricted to authorized employees who have a legitimate business purpose and reason for accessing it. As a condition of their employment, all employees of XXXBlackBook.com are required to follow this Policy. Employees are informed about the importance of privacy and they are required to agree to a code of conduct that prohibits the disclosure of any personal information to unauthorized individuals or parties. 

Unauthorized access to and/or disclosure of personal information by an employee of XXXBlackBook.com is strictly prohibited. All employees are expected to maintain the confidentiality of personal information at all times and failing to do so will result in appropriate disciplinary measures, which may include dismissal. 

#### 12) Our Commitment to Data Security.

The security of your personal information is a priority to XXXBlackBook.com. We are responsible for protecting personal information under our control, including personal information that has been transferred to, or received from, a third party.

Registered User and Member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. We use reasonable measures to protect registration and membership information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to User information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff, and such employees shall be required to respect the privacy of that information. 

In the event that personal information is transferred to a third party, XXXBlackBook.com will take steps to ensure that such recipients safeguard the personal information and use the information only for authorized purposes. Some examples of such measures are as follows:

  1. Physical security measures such as restricted access facilities and locked filing cabinets. 
  2. Electronic security measures for computerized personal information such as password protection, database encryption and personal identification numbers.
  3. Organizational processes such as limiting access to such personal information to a selected group of individuals.
  4. Contractual obligations with third parties who need access to personal information by agreements stipulating the confidentiality of the information and requiring them to protect and secure the personal information.

Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

#### 13) Our Commitment to Children's Privacy.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 18 years of age, and no part of XXXBlackBook.com is structured to attract anyone under 18 years of age. If you are younger than 18 years of age, you are not permitted to use this site.

#### 14) Websites Governed by this Privacy Policy.

The Website that is governed by the provisions and practices stated in this Policy is: XXXBlackBook.com. XXXBlackBook.com's Website may contain links to other third party sites that are not governed by this Policy. Although we endeavor to only link to sites with high privacy standards, our Policy will no longer apply once you leave XXXBlackBook.com's Website. Additionally, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other third party websites, nor are we responsible for the content of any such web property, company or organization that we do not control. Further, we cannot control and are not responsible for the actions of the employees, agents or assigns of any such web property, company or organization. Therefore, we suggest that you examine the privacy policies of those sites to learn how your information may be collected, used, shared and disclosed.

#### 15) Terms and Conditions, Notices and Revisions.

Your use of the Website, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Policy as well as our Terms and Conditions and all of its dispute resolution provisions including, but not limited to, limitations of liability and governing law.

#### 16) Updating this Privacy Policy. 

This Policy is subject to change by XXXBlackBook.com at any time. We may modify any of the terms contained in this Policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any changes to our privacy policy and information handling practices will be acknowledged in this policy in a timely manner. We may add, modify or remove portions of this policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so. You may determine when this policy was last updated by referring to the date at the bottom of this privacy policy. 

If any modification to this Policy is unacceptable to you, you agree that your only recourse is to terminate this Policy. Your continued use of the Service following our posting of a change notice or new agreement on the Website will constitute your binding acceptance of the change.

BY PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY.

#### 17) Handling Complaints, Questions and Suggestions. 

To stop or resume receiving email notifications regarding various site activity or offers, users can edit their settings at:  XXXBlackBook.com

If you have any further questions or concerns about XXXBlackBook.com's privacy policies and use of personal information, please contact us through:

By mail: 

XXXBlackBook.com

2nd Floor

13 Upper Baggot Street

Dublin 4, Ireland

Telephone: +353.15262707 Fax: +353.16335198 

#### 18) Dispute Resolution

Any claim or cause of action you may have arising from, connected with, or relating to this privacy policy or XXXBlackBook.com's handling of your personal information, or any related matters must be commenced within six (6) months after the claim or cause of action arises, after which time the claim or cause of action is forever barred, regardless of any statute or law to the contrary. 

Version [06/23/10]
